water4gas.com 2010-05-03

# Privacy Policy

Effective November 11, 2008 

**Privacy Policy Notice Table Of Contents:**

  1. Our Commitment To Privacy

  2. The Information We Collect
  3. How We Use Information
  4. Our Commitment To Data Security
  5. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  6. How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  7. How To Contact Us

 **Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Water4Gas [company name: 1 Freedom, Inc.] is committed to protecting your privacy. We are operating in accordance with the strictest security procedures for the storage and disclosure of information which you give us. Any personal information provided by you will be treated as confidential. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Water4Gas [company name: 1 Freedom, Inc.] website. When you register as a member, vendor or reader, when you enter a competition or promotion, subscribe to our newsletter or submit a business application - we may ask for your personal information so that we can administer services and notify winners. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number 

IMPORTANT NOTE: This website contains NO E-COMMERCE, so when you are being requested for any financial information such as credit card numbers, bank details, payment details such as PayPal or any other sensitive personal identity information, please be aware that it is NOT BEING REQUESTED ON OUR OWN WEBSITE and is therefore the responsibility of the third-party entity or entities (Independent Vendors including service providers) who's website may be linked from ours. This does not mean that these Independent Vendors or service providers are abusive of your information; it only means that you need to be aware that when you engage in commerce through our website, it is not Water4Gas collecting your financial information, but our approved Independent Vendors. WHEN USING OUR PRODUCT SELECTION GUIDE YOU ALWAYS ENGAGE IN COMMERCE WITH THIRD-PARTY(S).

 **The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself only to serve you better, however there is no e-commerce conducted on this website. We do not collect financial information. We do not share the information collected by us with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your request. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive, or to send back requested materials. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to become a member. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

WE WILL NOT SPAM YOU. Your name, email, phone, shopping history or any other personal information will never be sold, given to anyone else or rented. If you would prefer not to receive emails or other information from us, a facility is available to unsubscribe. Your info is well guarded in our computers by the latest online security technology, so your privacy is also well protected from hackers and data thieves.  

We absolutely keep our hands OFF of criminal practices such as "spyware" or "adware". We DO NOT sell, rent, loan, trade, lease or otherwise divulge the email addresses and postal addresses on our mailing list or customer list to anyone. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Any personal information collected will NOT be disclosed to any third party, except in the case of cooperating with law enforcement agencies to aid in identifying those persons using our services for illegal activities. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Since e-commerce (ordering Water4Gas products) is done through third parties only, we use only such services such (for example) as PayPal and ClickBank that have a commitment, firm policies and long track record for highest privacy and data security practices.

When you use our Product Selection Guide you may choose to order products or services RELATED TO Water4Gas but are actually delivered or rendered by third-party vendors, when you click an external link displayed on our Product Selection Guide, you will be taken to a third-party website. In such an event, you must verify that third-party's privacy and data security practices are satisfactory to your full satisfaction. Specifically be aware not to provide sensitive financial information such as credit card numbers, on a web page that is not secure, i.e., in its displayed URL it must have "https"(S at the end for "secured page") so you know your information is secured by the third-party's website.

However, the privacy and data security practices of third party companies is always their own responsibility and we expect you to shop responsibly when using third party that may be linked through our website.

 **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

If you are a Member on this website, you can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by signing into the Members Log-In area. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

If you are a book reader or subscriber to news, etc, you can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at the phone number displayed at our Contact Us page, or send us an email via the online email link on that page.
